<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" 
     title="AuthorProfile home">
  <div>
    We now have a prototype running. Look
    at our <a href="by_last_change_1.html">list of authors</a>.
    We use the profiles from the <a
    href="http://authorclaim.org/">AuthorClaim</a> registration
    service.
  </div>
  <h2>Vision</h2>
  <div>
    <div>for authors</div>
    <blockquote>
      <div>
        AuthorProfile builds a page or each academic author in
        the world, with all papers that they have written. When
        finished, it will be a replacement of the “papers published” part in
        academic CVs. All AuthorProfile data is freely reusable.
      </div>
    </blockquote>
  </div>
  <div>
    <div>for librarians</div>
    <blockquote>
      <div>
        AuthorProfile is a service that presents authors and the
        papers that they have written. It is different from a normal
        bibliographic database that lists papers and then the the
        papers’ authors. AuthorProfile places the prime focus on the
        author.
      </div>
    </blockquote>
  </div>
  <h2>more</h2>
  <div>
    James is in the process of addressing matters unrelated to the development of AuthorProfile.  As a result, he cannot commit to any development within the near future.
  </div>
  <div>
    02/28/12: James is continuing to develop the object-oriented API.  He is currently finishing the network exploration script in Python.  This will deprecate what has been developed in Perl for the "vertical integration calculations".  After this is functional, it will be moved to a BitBucket repository, and source code will be managed with the Git version control system.
  </div>
  <div>
    02/25/12: James has developed <a href="devel/jquery_search.html">a jQuery/AJAX search feature</a>.  It is still being developed.
  </div>
  <div>
    02/24/12: James has drafted an overview of the network exploration process: <a href="http://authorprofile.org/shortest_path_discovery_overview_draft.pdf">(the Adobe PDF)</a>.
  </div>
  <div>
    02/24/12: James has drafted an entity relationship diagram for the object-oriented revision of system processes: <a href="http://authorprofile.org/erd_draft.pdf">(the Adobe PDF)</a>.
  </div>
  <div>
    02/19/12: James has authored a <a href="http://authorprofile.org/faq.txt">F. A. Q.</a>
  </div>
  <div>
    We have some <a href="/doc/index.html">documentation</a>.
  </div>
</div>